Hi everyone, welcome to Lao E's channel
This season's Microsoft 365 Premium academic discount is still very practical.
First, the five-year subscription
First of all, for a five-year subscription at a monthly rate of $19.99,
That totals over $1000.
In addition, the premium version includes the entire Office suite.
1T OneDrive cloud storage
Additionally, using the latest ChatGPT 5.2-powered Microsoft Copilot
It is also unlimited and omnipresent.
It also allows us to add 5 family group members
Each member is independent
1T OneDrive cloud storage and more
Without further ado, let's get started
Before we start, please like and subscribe to Old E's channel
Support me in creating more and better content
Since the goal is 5 years, the Microsoft account we bind
which is our Outlook email
We need to check its account information
Don't be too outrageous, as I believe from an algorithmic perspective
This constitutes whether it's a 4-year or 5-year
such a criterion
Alright, let's open the Outlook email
Then click on the Settings in the upper right corner, the second option: Account
After opening the account, we click on the 'Manage' option on the right side
you can view your account information
including personal information, etc.
This is one method, the second method is to directly click on our avatar
then click on my Microsoft account
Then it opens my account management page
On the account management page, we can see it includes many
The second item is your information
Your info, we can take a look at your personal information
At the same time, we recommend checking the bottom section
Change its language to American English
which means changing your region to the US in Microsoft
the second item your info
the second item, Your info
We click on
What should you check? The key points are your date of birth and country/region.
Your birthday cannot be that of a fifty or sixty-year-old uncle
to apply for a student discount for a twenty-year-old
This is obviously not right.
If something seems off, why would I give you a five-year discount?
Of course
This is one-sided opinion
Logically speaking
That should be it. If there are any issues, you can make edits or modifications.
your linked Microsoft account
Step one and step two cannot be wrong
First, claim the Personal edition
Then, to claim the Premium version, we click on this link for the Personal version
It will directly jump to the corresponding page
Of course, I can also paste it into other browsers
for example, paste it into Chrome
I'll proceed with the claim. Now, let's look at the top left corner.
At the same time, if everyone hasn't switched the language
If you switch to American English, your interface should be different from mine
At least you won't have Google Pay
If we click next
Then we choose Google Pay as the payment method
Okay, now it starts loading
The second step is to verify our student email.
Of course, you can also modify your payment method here.
As for the displayed 12-month free trial
We can ignore this here
Our goal is not the personal edition, but the 5-year premium version.
If you don't have a personal email, you can also click here
use alternative methods for academic verification
for example, upload a student ID
upload transcript
Okay, here I enter Marry Cube's EDU email address
after entering the maricopa.edu email address
Click to verify email
Hold on a moment, there are a series of actions happening in the background.
Please note, there will be a line of small text prompting you
A verification link has been sent
to your bound email address
There won't be any page jump.
I opened my edu email
Open this email, we can directly click on the verification link here
Here, I just copied it and then
paste it into the address bar, or go back to the previous application page
Open a new tab and paste it in
Then, after a short wait, it will congratulate us on successfully claiming the offer.
First, it will display an academic verification status like this
We will soon be reminded
Congratulations, your academic status has been successfully verified.
Here, you can skip clicking 'Continue' and simply close this page.
It doesn't matter if you click it
After clicking it
Because it's checked out, it gives you the illusion
as if the discount is gone
That's not the case
because we haven't made the payment yet
Even if it's a zero-dollar purchase, I still have to go through with the zero-dollar purchase
I still have to pay, so even if you click
Don't panic when you see this page
Click the first step again, the link to redeem the personal version of Microsoft 365
After clicking, we will still see
still a personal
We haven't completed this yet
We haven't made the payment yet, so if you find that your payment method is missing
you just click again to add a new payment method
Open it and still select GPay
Please make sure to confirm that the language and region in the bottom left corner
Is it in American English to have GPay as an option?
After selecting GPay
At this point, there will be 'Add billing address'
Add a billing address
so we click on the one below
Add billing address
This billing address can be filled in randomly, but don't make it too outrageous
You can't just fill in your home street address here
It is a U.S. address
If you want to be lazy, this kind of laziness
That's definitely not correct. I'll enter a real U.S. address here
Then click Save, and you're done.
Wait a moment, it's loading, and after loading
then it will prompt you
It's done
You have succeeded
Verification completed, discount claimed
Then we click Start Trial
What is this
Start the payment, because we haven't paid yet.
Right, at this point, I'll bring up the GPay that I've already pre-bound.
Then check the box and click 'Pay Now'
After the payment is completed
After the payment, we will not demonstrate the subsequent processing steps.
Fast forward, and now we've successfully completed the first step of claiming the personal edition.
Then we reopen
The page after clicking looks like this
It prompts us that we are switching from Microsoft Personal to Premium.
What does the premium version include?
It prompts that we can expand this green notification bar
Here, I'll click Next
Here it prompts a one-month Free Trial
Ignore it
We add the payment method and then click Next
The addition of the payment method is the same as before
I'll quickly skip over it
After adding, it will still show loading
At this point, we won't be asked to add a billing address
but prompts us to Select and choose a billing address
We click to select the billing address
The following process is essentially the verification of academic status.
Of course, it no longer requires us to repeatedly submit the email.
it will directly inform us that the identity verification has been successful
Then we continue to click on 'Start Trial Pay Later'
Here,
We need to pay attention to the fact that its price is $19.99 per month
and it's under the annual payment plan
It's still the same
We still get it for free, but we need to make one payment. Click 'Pay Now'
Payment completed
Just a moment
We will soon receive a notification confirming our successful subscription.
It prompts us that we can start immediately
our one-month free Microsoft 365 Premium edition
Ignore it, even though it shows a one-month period here
However, we should refer to the subscription status in our Microsoft account as the authoritative source.
Okay
Here,
We emphasize two points. First, you must switch it to
American English
the US region of Microsoft, otherwise your interface
including options, many aspects
is different from mine. Secondly, it's the premium subscription for 365
the personal email account, and it is not bound to our
the EDU account we applied for in advance
Finally, don't forget to like and subscribe to Lao E's channel.
Okay
We open the mailbox and will see that we have two emails from Microsoft
The notifications for both the Personal and Advanced editions have been successfully processed.
Moreover, you will see at the top right corner of your email
you should see the Copilot icon
It is everywhere. Then we click on Me account
Me Microsoft account
On the Home page of the account, our subscription information will be clearly displayed
Next billing date: 2031
Five years achieved! Of course, what's displayed here is only
expiration date information
For more details, we can check the subscription on the left side
After clicking on it
We can see that, in addition to the 5-year subscription period until January 2031,
And also,
our billing information
$19.99 per month, along with 1TB of OneDrive storage
There are also other features, including a 5-person shared subscription, and so on.
So to avoid being taken advantage of
We can select the third option in the left navigation bar: Subscription
In the subscription
In addition to what we just mentioned, you can view detailed subscription information
Additionally, we can manage the subscription
Click on the management in the upper right corner
After opening it, we select the second last option to turn off recurring payments.
Well, that's all for this video share.
See you next time
Thank you